[
    {
        "question": "ويليام",
        "response": "مايليو"
    },
    {
        "question": "نامي",
        "response": " يمان"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوفي",
        "response": "يفول"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايرين",
        "response": "نيريا"
    },
    {
        "question": "استا",
        "response": "اتسا"
    },
    {
        "question": "همتارو",
        "response": "وراتمه"
    },
    {
        "question": "الويفيا",
        "response": "ايفيولا"  
    },
    {
        "question": "نويل",
        "response": "ليون"
    },
    {
        "question": "رايلي",
        "response": "يليار"
    },
    {
        "question": "ال",
        "response": "ل ا"
    },
    {
        "question": "لاو",
        "response": "وال"
    },
    {
        "question": "مادارا",
        "response": "ارادام"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوريتشي",
        "response": "يشتيروي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايتاتشي",
        "response": "يشتاتيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "توبي",
        "response": "يبوت"
    },
    {
        "question": "نوبارا",
        "response": "ارابون"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليفاي",
        "response": "يافيل"
    },
    {
        "question": "هاشيراما",
        "response": "اماريشاه"
    },
    {
        "question": "بوروتو",
        "response": "وتوروب"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوسوب",
        "response": "بوسوي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ريم",
        "response": "مير"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوتشيها شيسوي",
        "response": "يوسيش اهيشتوا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيد",
        "response": "ديك"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكاسا",
        "response": "اساكيم"
    },
    {
        "question": "دانزو",
        "response": "وزناد"
    },
    {
        "question": "وينغ",
        "response": "غنيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "تينشيهان",
        "response": "ناهيشنيت"
    },
    {
        "question": "بيكوهان",
        "response": "ناهوكيب"
    },
    {
        "question": "كازيكاجي",
        "response": "يجاكيزاك"
    },
    {
        "question": "جيرايا",
        "response": "اياريج"
    },
    {
        "question": "كازيكاجي",
        "response": "يجاكيزاك"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوكومي",
        "response": "يموكوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "غيو",
        "response": "ويغ"
    },
    {
        "question": "تشيو",
        "response": "ويشت"
    },
    {
        "question": "ساسوري",
        "response": "يروساس"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيزوكو",
        "response": "وكوزين"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميدوريا",
        "response": "ايروديم"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيجي",
        "response": "يجين"
    },
    {
        "question": "استا",
        "response": "اتسا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليزا",
        "response": "ازيل"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاغويا",
        "response": "ايوغاك"
    },
    {
        "question": "هينا",
        "response": "انيه"
    },
    {
        "question": "الوكا",
        "response": "اكولا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيناتا",
        "response": "اتانيه"
    },
    {
        "question": "زينتسو",
        "response": "وستنيز"
    },
    {
        "question": "رينغوكو",
        "response": "وكوغنير"
    },
    {
        "question": "ليفاي",
        "response": "يافيل"
    },
    {
        "question": "كورتا",
        "response": "اتروك"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيسوكا",
        "response": "اكوسيه"
    },
    {
       "question": "انوس",
        "response": "سونا"
    },
    {
       "question": "بياكوغان",
        "response": "ناغوكايب"
    },
    {
       "question": "شوكو",
        "response": "وكوش"
    },
    {
       "question": "ديكو",
        "response": "وكيد"
    },
    {
       "question": "يامي",
        "response": "يماي"
    },
    {
       "question": "فانجانس",
        "response": "سناجناف"
    },
    {
       "question": "يوليوس",
        "response": "سويلوي"
    },
    {
       "question": "تسوموغو",
        "response": "وغوموسوت"
    },
    {
       "question": "نانامي",
        "response": "يمانانا"
    },
    {
       "question": "ايزن",
        "response": "نزيا"
    },
    {
       "question": "زاراكي",
        "response": "يكاراز"
    },
    {
       "question": "اوراهارا",
        "response": "اراهاروا"
    },
    {
       "question": "اينوي",
        "response": "يونيا"
    },
    {
       "question": "غوهان",
        "response": "ناهوغ"
    },
    {
       "question": "كيريلين",
        "response": "نيليريك"
    },
    {
       "question": "هيناتسورو",
        "response": "وروستانيه"
    },
    {
       "question": "ريتشيل",
       "response":"ليشتير"
}
      ]